A Guide to the Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association Records, 1987-2001
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association Records, 1987-2001
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 05-73
0.5 linear feet
The Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association Records consists of 0.5 linear feet, spans the years 1987-2001 and contains meeting minutes, correspondence, calendars, and bylaws.
Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Donated by John Weidner, January 2020.
Historical and Biographical Information
In 1965, Camelot Builders Inc. purchased a large tract of land in West Springfield, Virginia and developed Orange Hunt Estates over a fifteen-year period from 1965 to 1980. The development consisted of single-family houses and townhouses bordered by Old Keene Mill Road and the present-day Fairfax County Parkway. Residents formed the Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association shortly after completion of the first homes in 1966. All residents are due-paying members of the association which exists to preserve the quality of life and property values of the community. The association implements safety and beautifying programs and holds general membership meetings a few times a year.
Scope and Content
The Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association Records consists of 0.5 linear feet, spans the years 1987-2001 and contains meeting minutes, correspondence, calendars, and bylaws. Meeting minutes from the board and general membership meetings are included. Subjects covered are the activities of the association.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Orange Hunt Estates Civic Association; Springfield (Va.) - History
Container List
- Board Members, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Calendar, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Calendar, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Forms, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Organization and Legal Documents, 1987-2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)